Raven's Hollow is a mystery, thriller, horror film
directed by Christopher Hatton.
West Point cadet Edgar Allan Poe and four other cadets on a training exercise in upstate New York are drawn by a
gruesome discovery into a forgotten community where they find a township guarding a frightening secret.
Charlotte Ingram, played by Melanie Zanetti.
Edgar Allan Poe, played by William Moseley.
Elizabet Ingram, played by Kate Dickie.
Dr. Garrett, played by David Hayman.
Will Taylor, played by Callum Woodhouse.
Daniel Clay, played by Callum McGowan.
Melanie Zanetti (born 20 March 1985) is an Australian actress.
She is best known as the voice of Chilli Heeler in the critically
acclaimed animated television program Bluey (2018–present).
She has also portrayed Charlotte Ingram in the horror film Raven's Hollow (2022), and Julia
Mitchell in the erotic romance film series Gabriel's Inferno (2020–2023).
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.